Contact

hilaryortega@ymail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hilary-ortega-b85111124 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Flexible Schedule
Inpatient Care
Mental Health

Hilary Ortega

PMHNP/FNP

Fort Lauderdale, Florida

Summary

Dual certified PMHNP-BC and FNP-C nurse practitioner with 8 years of nursing experience in various roles including travel experience. Well versed in multiple EMR systems and flexible in terms of schedule. Seeking an opportunity close to Fort Lauderdale, FL.

Experience

Fort Lauderdale Hospital
Psychiatric Nurse
April 2017 - August 2019 (2 years 5 months)
Miami/Fort Lauderdale Area

Broward General Hospital Registered Nurse Progressive Care July 2016 - March 2017 (9 months)

AB Staffing Solutions
Tavel nurse progressive care
August 2015 - June 2016 (11 months)
Varied

Accountable Healthcare Staffing Travel nurse stepdown/telemetry September 2014 - July 2015 (11 months) Varied

Methodist Specialty and Transplant Hospital Telemetry Float to Psychiatry RN February 2012 - August 2014 (2 years 7 months) San Antonio, Texas

Education

Regis College

Psychiatric Nurse Practitioner Post Masters Certificate, Psychiatric nurse practitioner · (2018 - 2019)

Chamberlain University

Family nurse practitioner · (2014 - 2017)